foods.tv 2015-04-19

# – Privacy Policy | Foods TV

This privacy policy applies to your use of the Foods.tv website and its applications for mobile devices (collectively, the “Site”), but does not apply to any third party sites that are linked to them, or any relationships you may maintain with the businesses on the Site.

The terms “we”, “us”, and “Foods.tv” refer to Online Discovery LLC. The terms “you” and “your” refer to you, as a user of the Site. The term “personal information” means information that you provide to us which allows us to contact or identify you, such as your name, your phone number, your email address, your current location or any other data that is connected to such information.

BY USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THESE TERMS, YOU SHOULD NOT USE THE SITE. 

###### **1\. COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to make sure that the collection of personal information is limited only to what is necessary in order to serve the purposes outlined below. If we plan to use your information for a manner other than the one which it is collected for, then we will ask you for your consent before we proceed to use it.

**Foods.tv Member Account.** If you create a member account on Foods.tv in order to take advantage of all the services offered on the Site, we may ask for and record personal information such as your name and email address. We use your email address to send you news and updates as well as notifications regarding other users’ actions on your contributed content (such as when other users like or dislike your contributed content or comment on your contributed content). 

**Added Content.** We store and may publicly display your added content on the Site in order to provide the services that we offer. When we display your content, we do so together with your account name (first name and last name), your current location and your profile photo. The term “added content” refers to the information that you submit or post to the Site for public display, such as business ratings, reviews, photos, videos, geo-tags, comments, business profile edits, spottings and the information that you display as part of your member profile.

**Feedback.** If you contact us to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, we will record any personal information and other content that you provide in your communication so that we can effectively respond to your communication.

**Activity.** We record information relating to your use of the Site, such as the searches you make, the pages you view, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp information. We use this type of information to administer the Site and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Site. You cannot be identified from this aggregate information.

**Cookies.** We send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely identify your browser and improve the quality of our service. The term “cookies” refers to small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing the site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Persistent cookies can be removed by following directions in your specific browser. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Site may not work properly.

**Enforcement.** We may use the information we collect in connection with your use of the Site (including your personal information) in order to investigate, enforce, and apply our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy. 

###### **2\. TRANSFER OF INFORMATION**

We may distribute your added content to third parties, as permitted pursuant to our Terms and Conditions of Use. The third parties may in turn publicly display or publish your added content in connection with their own websites and media platforms. When we distribute your added content to third parties, we may include your account name (but not your personal information unless you include it within your added content).

We may share your personal information with third parties to provide you with services that we offer through the Site, conduct quality assurance testing, facilitate creation of accounts, provide technical and customer support, or provide specific services in accordance with your instructions. These third parties are required not to use your personal information other than to provide the services requested by you.

We may share your personal information with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, “Affiliates”) that we may have now or in the future, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires our company or our assets, that company will possess your personal information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties in a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to:

  * (a) take action regarding suspected illegal activities
  * (b) enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions of Use and Privacy Policy
  * (c) comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order
  * (d) protect our rights, reputation, and property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public. 

Please note that we are not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena or other similar governmental request that we receive.

We may disclose information in the aggregate to third parties relating to user behavior in connection with actual or prospective business relationship with those third parties, such as advertisers and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, advertising banners.

We may use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

###### 3\. OTHER PEOPLE’S INFORMATION

You may choose to provide us with another person’s email address to invite the person to use the Site. We use this information to contact that person about the invitation only once, unless that person becomes a member on the Site or provides us with their email address again, either by subscribing to a newsletter or by other means. By providing us with another person’s e-mail address, you represent to us that you have obtained the consent of the person to share his or her e-mail address with us. All invitees are provided with the option not to receive further invitations. We may disclose such information if required to do so in order to comply with legal process, as described above. 

###### 4\. LINKS

The Site may contain links to third party websites to which we have no affiliation. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with those third parties, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites. 

###### 5\. CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

To the extent you include personal information within your submissions (such as a photo of yourself), third parties may be able to identify you, associate you with your user account, and contact you. Third parties can also associate you with your user account using the “Member Search” feature on the Site, but only if the third party already knows your full name and you include information in your submissions that allow the third party to distinguish you from other users who might share the same full name. Please do not include information in your submissions that you expect to keep private. In addition, you can reduce the risk of being personally identified by choosing a fictitious account name, though doing so may detract from the credibility of your submissions among other users.

As a registered Foods.tv member, you can modify some of your personal information by accessing the “Account” section of this website. 

If you close your account, we may still retain your personal information in our systems. 

###### 6\. SECURITY

Your account is password protected. We use industry standard measures to protect the personal information that is stored in our database. We limit the access to your personal information to those employees and contractors who need access to perform their job function, such as our customer service personnel. If you have any questions about the security on the Site, please contact us. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that your personal information will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

You hereby acknowledge that Foods.tv is not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.

###### 7\. NAI Opt Out Procedures

Customized or interest based advertising is a commonly used set of technologies that allow advertising platforms to provide you with advertisements more closely tailored to your interests. The Network Advertising Initiative is a coalition of online media firms that allow you to opt-out of customized advertisements within your browser.  
You can learn about which NAI member firms are customizing advertisements for your browser and choose to opt out of customized advertising of this type by going to the following link: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

###### 8\. TERMS AND MODIFICATIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and will post any new versions on this page. If we make any material changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by sending an e-mail to the last email address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website. Any such changes will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our website. These changes will be effective immediately for new users of the Site. Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your personal information to provide us with your most current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of personal information that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your personal information, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with us. Continued use of the Site following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. 

###### 9\. DISPUTE RESOLUTION

If you believe that Foods.tv has not adhered to this Privacy Policy you may write to Foods.tv at [privacy@mvs.tv](mailto:privacy@mvs.tv). In your correspondence, please describe in as much detail as possible ways in which you believe the Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly. 

###### 10\. CONTACTING THE WEBSITE AND ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of this website, or if you want to exercise any of the rights that you are given under this Privacy Policy, you can contact us using the contact information listed above.
